Hello

I'm Okongo Eugine

Nairobi, +254 741 505 192 okongoeugine84@gmail.com

About Me

I am a dedicated cybersecurity professional with training in ethical hacking and offensive cybersecurity. My recent completion of a comprehensive program in cybersecurity has equipped me with an understanding of network security, penetration testing, vulnerability assessment, and threat analysis.

I am committed to continuous learning and staying ahead of emerging cyber threats. My goal is to leverage my technical expertise and analytical thinking to contribute to the protection of organizations and their assets from sophisticated cyber attacks

Skills

Cyber Security

Securing digital assets.

Red Teaming

Web Development

penetration testing

Vulnerability Assessment

Experience

April 2024- May 2024

Cyber Talents- *cybersecurity and CTF Player*

- Kali Linux practitioner.
- Completion of labs.
- Use of burp suite.
- Web Application security

May 2024- July 2024

Cyber Forensics & Security Solutions - offensive cyber security

- Cyber security project.
- Use of open source tools in kali linux.

September 2024

IBM, Karen- BootCamp

- Fundamentals of Cyber security.
- Web development.

Education

September 2022 - present

Catholic University of Eastern Africa, Karen - Bachelor's degree Computer Science.

Awards

Cyber Talents Certificate.

Cyber Forensic & Security Solutions Certificate.

IBM Certificate.